const css = [
    {
        id:1,
        question:"The full form of CSS is :",
        options:[
            {1:"Cascading Style Sheets"},
            {2:"Coloured Special Sheets"},
            {3:"Color and Style Sheets"},
            {4:"None of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"Cascading Style Sheets"
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:"How can we change the background color of an element?",
        options:[
            {1:"background-color"},
            {2:"color"},
            {3:"Both A and B"},
            {4:"None of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"background-color"
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:"What type of CSS is generally recommended for designing large web pages?",
        options:[
            {1:"Inline"},
            {2:"Internal"},
            {3:"External"},
            {4:"None of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"External"
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:"Which HTML tag is used to declare internal CSS?",
        options:[
            {1:"<style>"},
            {2:"<link>"},
            {3:"<script>"},
            {4:"None of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"<style>"
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:"How can we select an element with a specific ID in CSS",
        options:[
            {1:"#"},
            {2:"."},
            {3:"^"},
            {4:"None of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"#"
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:"How can we write comments in CSS?",
        options:[
            {1:"/**/"},
            {2:"//"},
            {3:"#"},
            {4:"All of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"/**/"
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:"Can negative values allowed in padding property",
        options:[
            {1:"Yes"},
            {2:"No"},
            {3:"Depends on property"},
            {4:"None of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"No"
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:"How can we specify the spacing between each letter in a text in CSS",
        options:[
            {1:"alpha-spacing"},
            {2:"letter-spacing"},
            {3:"character-spacing"},
            {4:"None of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"letter-spacing"
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:"We can make rounded borders around elements using which CSS elements?",
        options:[
            {1:"border-collapse"},
            {2:"border-round"},
            {3:"border-radius"},
            {4:"None of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"border-radius"
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:"Which of the following are valid CSS position property values?",
        options:[
            {1:"static"},
            {2:"relative"},
            {3:"fixed"},
            {4:"All of the above"},
        ],
        correct:"All of the above"
    },
    
]

export default css